Hi, this is John Sonmez from Pluralsight and in this module we'll be creating a simple Hello World
extension for Chrome. Chrome extensions themselves are pretty easy to create.
But, all the extra JavaScript and functionality inside of an extension can make it seem much more complex.
To avoid any of this complexity, we'll be creating a very basic browser action extension that just shows a
basic UI where a user can type in their name and see it echoed back to them with a greeting.
This basic extension will help us understand how extensions are put together and get us some experience
with going through that process before creating a more complicated extension like we'll do
in the following modules. By the end of this module you should understand the components you need
in order to create a Chrome extension and know how to add an extension you're developing
to an instance of Chrome to test it out.