Now, just as you might except, we can also add CSS. We could put that in line into our HTML or we can
just go ahead and create a new style sheet.
I'm just going to create a style sheet; we're just going to call this popup.css.
And we're just going to put a simple style in here just to show how this works.
So, I'll just go ahead and edit this.
And we're just going to put in this popup.css one small style here on the h1, we're just going to make
it so that the color for our text is basically going to just be blue.
So, we'll just put that in and then we're just going to go into our popup.html and we'll just add a reference
to our style sheet. We'll do this just like you would for any other HTML page.
We're just going to do a link rel=stylesheet and then type=text/css. And then the actual href for this.
And we're just going to put popup.css.
Now, one thing to note here, is that we are doing this relative because everything is in the same directory.
So, whenever we're referencing something, we're just basically referencing it without any kind of path here.
It's just a relative reference. So, this should reference our CSS.
So now, if we go ahead and save this, we can go ahead and open up a Chrome browser.
And inside here if we click on our pop-up, now you can see its being styled, it's coming up in blue.
And we're going to get into this more when we look at the Chrome developer tools.
But, I do want to show you, real quick, that if you wanted to use the Chrome DevTools on this,
the easiest thing to do is just to go to Inspect element.
And then you can see it'll pop-up a little version of the DevTools that's basically targeting this.
It's not the actual page itself. You just bring up the Chrome DevTools on the page; you're not going to
see the right thing. But you can use this to do some debugging and like I said in the last module,
we'll get into this much more.