Extensions can be as simple as a single manifest file and an HTML or JavaScript file.
But, most extensions will make use of several different kinds of files to create the desired functionality.
To start creating an extension you just need to create a directory in which you'll put all the files that
extension will use. In this directory you'll have to at least have a manifest file which is a JSON formatted
file that describes the properties of the extension. If your extension is going to have a user interface,
you'll probably need to include one or more HDML files in the directory as well.
Extensions can also have icons which are used in the Chrome store and the manage extensions tab in Chrome
and to display the extension in the Chrome toolbar. Those icon files should also be included in this
extensions directory. JavaScript files, CSS, and Images or any other files needed by the extension can
be included in there as well. Everything in the directory can be referenced using relative paths starting
from this directory. So, the Chrome extension directory is like a self-contained HTML application.