The first thing we'll need to create our Hello World extension will be the manifest file.
The manifest file will describe our extension and reference the HTML file we'll be using to display our
UI when someone clicks our extension icon in the toolbar. The manifest file uses the JSON format as you can
see in this example. So, it's pretty easy to read. At a minimum, a manifest file must have the manifest
version properties specified, which in our case will be 2. The name property which is the name of the extension,
and the version property which is the version number for your extension.
A description and any icon files are optional, but you should probably include those properties if you're
going to put the extension in the Chrome Web Store. Also, in the manifest file, we can specify whether
an extension will be a browser action or a page action or neither.
Remember, a browser action is going to show an icon in the toolbar that can be clicked to activate the extension,
while a page action will show an icon in the address bar of certain pages.
We can also specify the background page for an extension if it has one, or the context scripts the extension
will use if it has those, as well as an options page, permissions, and a pretty large list of other
properties for the extension. You can find a complete list of all the properties of a manifest file here.
It's a good idea to read through this list at some point so that you can understand all the capabilities
that can be defined in the manifest file.