So, the first thing that we'll need to do to create our extension is to go ahead and create a folder
that we're going to create the extension in. So, we're just going to create a folder here called Hello World.
And inside here we're going to place all of our files.
And the file that we're going to start with is our manifest file.
So, I'm just going to go ahead and create a New Text Document.
And I'm just going to call this manifest.json.
Now, let's go ahead and edit this. Now, you can edit this in any editor that you like.
I'm going to go ahead and use Visual Studio.
So, just go ahead and open up this file.
And what we're going to do with this manifest file is we need to add everything for our extension.
So, I'm going to go through this step-by-step. The first thing that we're going want is our manifest
version, so I'm just going to do this in a JSON format.
So, I'm going to say manifest_version:2 and then comma, and then we're going to add each property just like this.
So, this manifest version 2 is going to specify that this is version 2 of the manifest.json format.
And that's the version, the current version that we want to use.
Then we're going to specify the name of our extension which we're just going to call this Hello World.
And then we're going to specify what the description is, so we'll use this description property.
And we're going to say this is my fist Chrome extension. And we're going to skip the icon for the actual
extension itself at this point since we're not really going be installing this anywhere.
But, we will put an icon for our actual browser action which we'll discuss here in a minute.
So, after we have our description we want to put in our inversion.
This one is required and we're just going to make this be version 1.0.
And then in the next section we're going to make this a browser action.
Remember that a browser action is going to mean that this extension is going to be a button that's going to
be available at the Chrome toolbar and that's how we're going to activate this.
So, in order to do this, we're actually going to make an object inside here that's going to have some properties.
So, we're going to say browser_action and then we're going to use these brackets to indicate that this is
another JavaScript object in this JSON or JavaScript object notation.
So, you can think of this as sort of like sub-properties. So, for browser action we're going to specify
what the default icon should be and in our case it's going to be icon.png.
So, we're going to need to make an icon, and we'll do that a little bit later.
And our icon will actually need to be 19x19 pixels. And then we want to specify what our HTML page that
is going to be shown when someone clicks this browser action.
So, we're going to say default_popup and we're going to set this equal to popup.html.
So, we'll need to go ahead and create an HTML file called popup.html and put in our directory.
So, that's all we're going to do for our manifest file.
Just to recap this real quick, we have our manifest version, we've got our information about our actual
extension including the name description and the version number of the actual extension,
and then this browser action. Remember we could actually have a browser action or a page action or
neither of those, but in our case we're using browser action which means that it's going to be one
of those extensions that's going to appear in the toolbar and when we click it, it's going to display something.
So, the icon it's going to show is going to be this icon.png and when we click it
it's going to show this popup.html. So, we'll need to create that popup.html.
And this is just a very, very simple manifest file, of course, like we had discussed you can add a lot
more options to a manifest file. And you can check out that documentation on the manifest files to find
out more about what is available.