Okay, so now let's go ahead and create our HTML file. Remember that we need to have a popup.html, that is
what we had specified in our manifest.json.
So, I'm just going to do a new text document.
And I'm just going to call this popup.html.
And then we're just going to edit this HTML page.
So again, I'm opening this up in Visual Studio, but you can use whatever editor that you'd like.
And remember, this is just a basic HTML document. So, I'm just going to do the doc-type declaration
so, doctype html. And then I'm going to add the HTML tag.
And then we want to have a head, and inside our head we're going to add a title.
And we'll just call this Hello World. And then inside here we could add some styling if we wanted to.
And we can add our scripts in here, but right now let's go ahead and finish creating the rest of this.
So, let's put after our head, our body. And then for our page, let's actually just make an h1.
And we'll give this an ID, we'll call this greeting. And then we'll default this to be hi.
And then let's go ahead and make an input box here so, we're going to say input=name for the ID
and then the type will be equal to text. So, we'll have one text input box and that's it.
That'll be our basic HTML page. And a little tip here, if you use Windows,
you can actually set up your preview mode in Windows so that when you click on an HTML file,
it'll show you the preview of it and actually render that HTML which is pretty neat.
Especially when you're designing some HTML like this where you can't easily just test this out
in the actual extension. You can just open this up in a browser as well if you want to.
But the way that you do this is just go to Organize and then Layout and then check this Preview pane.
You'll notice that if I turn that off and then I go back in here and turn this on, it'll show that preview.
I tend to like this for a lot of different files that'll give you a preview which is nice.
For a video, it actually gives you a video player here that you can click Play.