Okay, so at this point we can almost preview our extension by loading it into Chrome.
The only thing that we really need in order to do this at this point is our
PNG for our icon. So, I'm going to go ahead and go to our directory here.
And I've already created an icon.png, I'm just going to Paste this in here.
Let's take a look at that real quick. It's just a picture of a world here for our Hello World
that I just created. It's just a 19x19 pixel icon.
It's a PNG file. So, that's specified in our manifest.json file which we're definitely going to need
in order to be able to load this and test this out. And so, let's go ahead and go to our browser.
And what I'm going to do here is I'm going to go ahead and go to extensions.
So, we're just going to do chrome://extensions and then I'm going to switch Developer mode on.
So, by default this will be off. It we click Developer mode you'll see this Load unpacked extension.
We can go here and we can just browse to the directory that contains our extensions.
So, this Hello World directory.
So, then I'm going to click OK. And now you can see it's loaded this extension and we can see that it
is set up, it's Enabled. We can remove it here if we want to. And you should see it show up in the bar now.
So now, if I click this, you can see it shows this HTML. That's all we really need to create an extension
at this point. Now, we're going to add a little bit more functionality to our extension just to see how things work.
We're going to keep things pretty simple, but that's really the basics.
We just have a manifest file that specifies an icon that specifies the HTML and we just have a simple HTML page.
You can make an extension that is really this simple.