Okay, so what we're going to do at this point is we're going to add some JavaScript.
And what we're going to do is we're going to add some JavaScript to add this functionality that's going to
make it so that when a user types their name into that input box, it's going to echo their name back
and say Hi, and then whatever their name is. So, in order to do this, we're actually going to use
jQuery, and then we're also going to use own JavaScript.
So, the first thing I'm going to do is show you how to get jQuery added to our extension.
This is pretty simple, all we're going to do is basically just go to jQuery.
So, we're just going to the jquery.com.
And then we're just going to download jQuery.
And you can get whichever you want, the compressed or uncompressed;
it doesn't really make much of a difference for an extension, so I'm just going to get the uncompressed version.
And I'm just going to go ahead and do a Save as here.
And I'm going to save this.
And I'm actually just going to save this right to that folder.
So, let's just go right into here in Hello World
and we're just going to Save this.
Okay, so now we have jQuery. And then the next thing we're going to do is create our own JavaScript file
that we're going to utilize here. So, let's go ahead and do New, Text Document.
And we're just going to call this popup.js.
And we'll need to go ahead and add this functionality, so I'm going to edit this.
And I've got Visual Studio open here and what we're going to want to do is include our jQuery file as
well as our popup.js. So, we're just going to do this just like we would do in any normal HTML page.
We're going to include our script here, right inside of the head.
So, we're just going to say script src=jquery let's go ahead and get the correct name for this.
So that will include jQuery and do remember with the script tags that you do have to use this closing
script or you might have some problems. And then we're going to do another one and we're just going to say
src=popup.js and that will include our popup.js. So, now let's go ahead and edit our popup.js.
And what we're going to do inside this popup.js is we're basically just going to create some
real simple functionality. I'm using jQuery here, you don't have to use jQuery if you don't want to jQuery.
But, I do find it a little bit easier to create JavaScript functionality like this with jQuery.
So, I'm basically setting this up so that this is going to run on document ready, this function that
we're specifying here, and then what I'm going to do is I'm going to grab our element with the ID name
which is going to be our input box, and I'm going to register an event handler for keyup.
So, basically whenever you type into that box when the key is up, after you're done typing, it's going
to execute this particular function. So, we're just going to create our function here.
And inside this function, what we want to do is we're going to want to echo back that name.
So, I'm going to go ahead and get our greeting which will be our h1,
and I'm going to set the text=Hi comma space and then I'm going to do a plus here, and I'm just going
grab that name again. So, we're going to get the text that's in there.
So, we're going to say name.val which will get the value of the name and then we're going to add an exclamation.
So, that's it. Some really simple functionality, not a lot to this, but let's go ahead and test this out.
Now, the nice thing about testing this out is we don't actually have to reload this inside our browser.
It's going to automatically reload for us.