So what we're going to do next is we're going to make it so that
when this is clicked, we're going to go ahead and check to see if there's a total already stored and we're
going to use the Chrome Storage API and then if there is, we're going to add the amount that's in that
amount box to that total. And if there's not, then we're just going to use the amount from the amount box
and we're going to save that value. So, in order to do this though, we're going to need to modify our
manifest file, because we need to add permissions to actually utilize the Storage API.
You always have to add permissions for whatever you're trying to do, so we're going to add this permissions
section and then we're going to actually use an array here, so we specify our permissions in this array,
and each type of thing has a specific permission; you can find this in the documentation on the API.
So that API doc that we had looked at before for the chrome APIs is going to say what permissions anything needs,
and in this case, we need permissions to storage. So once we have that, now we can use the Storage API in
our actual JavaScript. So what we're going to do here is we're going to start off by creating a variable
that's going to hold the new total, but we're going to want to try and get the value first, and everything
that we're going to do with the Chrome API is going to be pretty much using callbacks, because most of the
API is asynchronous. So that's important to know is that you're not going to get a result back;
if you're used to writing a lot of JavaScript code, that's probably nothing new to you, you're probably
familiar with that, but if you're not, then you have to get used to this asynchronous pattern.
So we're going to do chrome.storage.sync.get. Now, what we're using here is chrome.storage.sync;
there's also a chrome.storage.local. The difference is that the sync is going to get the data,
you can think of this from the cloud — it's going to automatically sync with other browser instances that
you might have, so when you save and get data it's getting it from there.
If you do local, it's just going to store it on the local instance.
If there is not a connection, the chrome.storage.sync is going to basically degrade to the local.
So, you probably want to use sync if you want to have data possibly be synced up; you only want to use local
if you're sure that you only want it to be stored locally. So here what we're going to pass is we can
either pass an array of strings or just a string for the key that we want.
So, let's just do our total here and then we pass in a function and this function is actually going to
return back the items, this is going to be an object, and it's going to have a property equal to each key
that gets returned. So what we're going to want to do next is create a variable called newTotal and we're
just going to set this equal to 0 for now, and then what we're going to do is we're going to check to see
if(items.total), then we know that something came back or there was something stored.
If this is false, we know that when we did the sync.get, there wasn't actually a total that was stored,
so we're not going to try and get that value, but if there is a value in there then what we want to do is
we want to set the newTotal += parseInt and we're going to parse items.total just to make sure that we get
this as an integer. So basically all this will do is if there is a total stored, we're going to get it and
that's going to be equal to our newTotal. Now, the next thing we want to do is get our amount.
So, we're going to do our $(‘#amount') and we're going to be getting the value of this, so this is going to
get our amount from our user interface that hopefully a user has entered in and we're going to check to see.
If there is an amount, then we're going to do something; if there's not an amount, we're not going to try
and add that amount to the total. So, if there amount, then we're going to say newTotal += and we'll do our
parseInt again to make sure we get this as an integer and we're going to parseInt our amount.
Okay, so now at this point we should have our total and it should take into account what the old total was,
if there was one already stored, otherwise it's just going to be adding that amount to 0, basically storing a new total.
So now we want to store this, and in this case, when we store it we don't really care about the callback,
because we can just send this store and we don't care when exactly it happens, we don't need to do anything
when this is done, so we're just going to do chrome.storage.sync.set and here we need to pass in an object
and we have to set the properties. So this is sort of like the reverse of what we're getting from the sync.get.
So we're just going to basically put here total and then we're going to use newTotal as the value for that property
and that's it — that should store this. Now we're going to do a little bit of cleanup here.
Let's go ahead and set the total text, because remember that we're going to have a new total here so we want
to actually set the text in our user interface equal to the newTotal and then let's go ahead and do
something to this amount, let's go ahead and blank this out. So we're going to say (‘#amount').val equals
an empty string just to indicate that we've actually stored that newTotal, we've added that amount.
Okay, then let's go ahead and end this function call, remember this is all inside of this function.
So we have to use the correct syntax here and so now this looks correct.
We're basically making it so that when addAmount is clicked, we're going to try and get the total,
we're going to try and add that total to our newTotal, which starts out at 0, we'll add the amount if there is
an amount, and then we're just going to store this newTotal, update the UI, and then blank out that amount.