Okay, so now before we can test this we have to do something special here.
With HTML and JavaScript, if you change those files, you don't really have to do anything because their
changes are going to be automatically reflected, but since we've added a permission, we actually have to go
here into Extensions and we have to click this Reload to reload the extension
and that's going to make sure that it gets that new permission that is needed for it.
So, now if we go to our extension and we type in an amount, click Add, you can see that it adds the protein,
but you'll notice one problem here - so if we close our extension and then reopen this UI, it doesn't show
us the total, so we can fix that real quick. What we need to do is load that amount when our page first loads.
So, all we have to do is inside here we're going to go ahead and do a chrome.storage.sync.get and then here
again we're just going to do this just like we did before, get our total, and then do function (items) and
then inside here what we want to do is we want to basically just set the (‘#total').text equal to items.total.
So now I can go ahead and save that and let's make sure that this is closed, and now if we open up our extension,
you can see that the Total automatically is showing up and it's going to reflect whatever the current total is.