Okay, so next we're going to add an Options page. In order to do that, what we're going to need to do is
to go into our manifest.json and we're going to have to add the entry for what the Options page is.
Every single extension that we create can have an Options page; we just have to specify that as a property
in our manifest. So let's go ahead and add this here and all we have to do is specify here options_page
and then the name of what that options page is going to be, so we're just going to call this options.html,
and then we'll go ahead and create an options.html in our directory.
So let's go ahead and open our directory and we'll just do a new, in fact let's just go ahead and copy our
popup.html to give us a bit of a head start here and we'll call this options.html, and then let's go ahead
and open this up in our Editor, and now we can go ahead and implement our options.
So, for our Options page, we're just going to make a real simple UI that's going to show what the goal is
in an input textbox that the user can change that goal and then we're going to have a button for saving
and one for resetting the total. So let's go ahead and change this title to Protein Tracker Options,
and then for our script, we're going to include jQuery, but let's also include this options.js, so we'll
have to create some JavaScript for our page and then we'll just call this Protein Tracker Options and then
here let's go ahead and leave our h2, and instead of having a span here, let's go ahead and put an input.
This way we'll have our input here that someone can enter the goal amount and we can save it from getting it
from this input. We'll want to change this id as well, so let's make this id be goal and then let's go ahead
and add our buttons, so we're going to have one button for saving, so we'll give this the id of save and
we'll give a value here of Save, and then let's add another button right below this, which we'll call our
reset button and the value for this one will be Reset Total.
So now let's just go ahead and check out our UI here in our Explorer window.
So if we go ahead and open this up, we can see that this looks okay - not the prettiest user interface,
but this should work for our Protein Tracker Options.
And then we're going to need that JavaScript file as well, so let's go ahead and we're just going to copy
and paste this one and we'll call this one options.js.
And then we need to implement this functionality for our options, which we'll do next.