Okay, so let's go ahead and clear out some of this that we have in our options.js so we can implement the logic
we want here. Now, the first thing that we're going to want to do is we're going to want to populate that
goal input if we have a goal, so we're actually going to change this; instead of doing chrome.storage.sync.get total,
let's go ahead and say get the goal. And then here we have a goal input and we're going to change the text,
and in this case since it's an input, it'll be the val, so we'll change the value equal to items.goal.
Now if there isn't already a goal saved, then that's fine - it's not actually going to do anything.
So then the next thing we're going to do is we're going to hook up the Save button.
So we want to go ahead and say when you click the save button and execute this JavaScript function, and inside here,
what we want to do is we want to go ahead and save that goal using the chrome storage.
So let's create a variable goal and we're going to set this equal to whatever the goal text is, so we use
this val to get that, and then if(goal), so if there's actually something entered there, then we can go ahead
and do chrome.storage.sync.set, and then remember here we pass in an object, so we just specify whatever
properties we want for this, we want it to have a property called goal, that'll be our key, and then it'll
be equal to whatever the goal is, and then we're actually going to create a callback here.
So when this finishes, when it's done saving, then we're going to go ahead and close the browser window,
or rather, we're going to close the tab; so we're going to do close here, so that should close that tab.
Then, there's one more thing we want to implement, we want to implement this reset functionality.
So let's go ahead and do that as well, so we're going to say (‘#reset').click and then here we're going to pass in
a function, and inside reset what we're going to want to do is for now all we're going to do is we're just
going to reset the total, so we're basically going to do chrome.storage.sync.set, and then we're going to
set the total property equal to 0. Now later on we'll actually make this show notification, but for now
we're just going to set the total to 0. So let's go ahead and test this out next.