Okay, so in our browser now, if we click our extension, we've got our Protein Tracker UI coming up,
and if we right-click here, we should be seeing Options. Now we're not going to see Options just yet,
because we haven't reloaded this plug-in. Again, we've changed the manifest file so we do need to reload this,
so let's go ahead and go to reload here and now if we right-click here we see Options and when we click that
you'll notice it opens up a new tab that has our Options. So now we can type in a Goal, let's say we put in 100,
and if we click Save, it closes that. Now we don't have this Goal showing up here; we'll need to implement
that functionality, but our Options page should work. So if we right-click, go to Options, you can see the
Goal is populated at 100 there. We should also be able to reset the Total, so right now our Total is 38.
So let's go ahead and click this Reset Total, and now you can see that the Total is 0.
So we have most of that functionality working; at this point the only thing we really need to add is the
ability to show this goal here, so that shows up in this UI. So let's go ahead and do that real quick.
What we want to do for this is we're just going to go back into our popup.html and what we want to do is
we want to populate this here. So we're going to need to put in a value and let's just call this id goal
and then we want to go into our popup.js, and here, the way that we're going to do this is we're going to
get back both the total and the goal at the same time here when we first load up this page.
So, instead of just passing in a string, we can pass in an array of strings, and we do that in JavaScript notation,
like this with the brackets, so we're going to ask for goal and total.
So we should get back both of those things and then all we're going to do here is we're just going to say,
okay, give us the goal, set the text equal to items.goal, and that should pretty much do it.
Let's go ahead and open up our browser window.
And we should just be able to go here now and we can see our Goal.
So now if we go to Options, let's change this to, say 150 and save it, and then we'll re-open up our extension,
and you can see that the goal is set to 150. We can still add protein, that works, and we should see our goal in our Options.