So next up we want to add some notifications. Right now when we click Reset in our options, it's not very
clear to the user that their total was reset, and since this is a destructive action we should probably
notify them in some way. So what we're going to do is we're going to use notifications to do that.
So in order to be able to use notifications, we have to add a permission, so we're going to go to our permissions,
and in addition to storage, we're going to add notifications. So this will give us access to the
Notification API inside of chrome and then what we're going to do, it's going to be pretty simple,
all we're going to do is in our options.js when we do this reset, instead of just doing this and forgetting about it,
we're going to go ahead and do a callback, so we're going to pass in this function, and inside here what we
want to do is we want to call chrome.notifications.create to create a notification.
So we're just going to do this var opt to make an object that's going to contain the options for our notification.
We could do this inline as well, but there's a lot here so it's nice to create the object outside in
a separate variable. So we're going to save that, first of all the type, and this is going to be basic.
So there's a few different types of notifications, we're not going to get into the different types here,
but you could check that out in the chrome APIs, and then we're going to set the title for the notification,
which is going to be "Total reset!" and then we're going to set the message.
So this is the message that will be displayed and we're going to say "Total has been reset back to 0."
And then we can specify what the icon URL is, and in our case, we're just going to use the one icon that we have.
It's going to look a little bit weird because it's going to blow it up, but you can create another icon if
you want to, you can customize any of these things; in fact, you might want to have different icons for
different types of notifications that you would use in your app.
So then we're going to call chrome.notifications.create and here what we want to do is specify an id for
that particular notification so we can uniquely identify it and then the options.
So, we're just going to call this one reset for the id and then we're going to pass in our options and then
we can pass in a callback, and I believe this one requires you to have a callback parameter, so we're just
going to pass in an empty function, we don't actually care to have a callback in our case.
So, now we should see a little notification show up at the bottom of the screen when we click the reset.
Now this is only going to work, I believe, on Windows and on Chrome OS right now.
I don't think notifications are implemented on the other operating systems and that may change by the time
that you're listening to this course, so don't be surprised if notifications don't work if you're not using
Windows or Chrome OS. Okay, so let's go ahead and go back to our browser and then remember we've changed
the permissions here, so we're going to need to reload this. So let's go ahead and go into our extensions,
and then we're going to go ahead and reload this extension, and then now, if we right-click here and go to Options
and we click Reset Total, there you go, you can see this Total reset, Total has been Reset back to 0.
And you can see it's blown up this icon, so if you actually had an icon of a larger size, this would show up
a little bit better in here, but this is the basic way to create notifications, which this is a pretty useful
feature of Chrome to be able to access these notifications. You can actually make it so that when a user
clicks on that notification, it does something, maybe it takes you to an option page or something like that,
and you can also update those notifications if you want through that API.