Okay now let's go ahead and add one more notification; we're going to do this in a very similar way as we
did the last one. What we're going to do is we're going to create a notification when the total is equal to
or exceeds the goal. So when the user has reached their goal, we want to show them a notification.
So all we're going to do this time is we're going to go into our popup.js and then inside here where we're
adding the amount, we want to check to see if the new total is going to be greater than the goal.
So, we're going to need to get the goal, so we're going to go ahead and change this so we're getting the
total and the goal. And then we're just going to simply do a check here, so we're just going to say,
if(newTotal &gt;= items.goal), then let's go ahead and show a notification that says that they've met their goal.
So let's go ahead and copy this and change this.
And we still want the type to be basic; we're going to say here "Goal reached!" and then for our message,
let's go ahead and make this be "You reached your goal of" and then let's put here items.goal and then an
exclamation mark. So then we're going to still use this icon.png; again, you could use different icons for
different notifications if you wanted to. And then we want to actually do the notifying, so we're going to
call chrome.notifications.create and then we'll give this an id. For this one, let's call it goalReached
and then we pass in our options and then a blank function, because we're not going to do anything when this completes.
So now we can go ahead and save that and let's go ahead and
open up our browser and now let's see what we have — we have a goal of 150.
So, if we put in an amount of, let's say 100, we get a total of 100, but now if I put in 60, you can see
"Goal reached! You reached your goal of 150."