Often when creating an extension, you'll need some JavaScript code to run when the extension first loads
before a user clicks the icon in the toolbar. In that case, a Background Page is needed.
As we talked about earlier, there are two types of background pages - persistent ones called Background Pages
and Event Pages, which are only activated at certain times. In most cases, you can get away with just using
an Event Page and it's preferred because it takes up less resources.
We'll be using an Event Page in our extension to register for any changes to the protein total and
update the badge that shows the current total, like you can see here, any time it changes.
We'll also use the Event Page to register a new context menu item, like you can see here,
that will be displayed when a user has selected some text and right-clicks.
We'll add an event handler that will respond to that menu item being selected,
which will attempt to add the selected text as a protein amount if the text is a number.