Okay, so now to do the next step, which is we're going to basically add a badge that's going to show what
the current protein count is; we're actually going to make use of an Event Page.
So the way that we do this is we have to go to our manifest, and inside here, we can specify the background,
and this is called background because there used to only be background pages and now background pages and
event pages are specified here. So, what we're going to do is we're going to create a background property,
and inside here, we're going to create an object that has our options.
So we put our scripts in here and this is going to be an array of the scripts that are going to be loaded;
we're just going to make our script called eventPage.js. And then we need to specify whether this is persistent,
so we're going to say persistent equals false. Now if you made persistent true, it would actually be a background page;
by making persistent false, it's an event page. So it's not going to live forever, it's only going to be
invoked when it's needed. Basically what we're going to do with our event page is we're going to register
some event handlers, we're going to listen for certain things, and that's what we're going to do in that
script, and then it will get invoked whenever those events fire.
If you just use the background page, you would have it running all the time so you wouldn't necessarily
have to listen for a specific event; you could have that page going pretty much all the time in the background.
And there are some cases where you'd want to do that, but in most cases you want to try and use the event page
instead because it's going to take up less resources. So, now the next thing we need to do is to go ahead
and create this eventPage.js. So let's go ahead and do a ‘New Text Document' and we'll just call this eventPage.js.
And now let's go ahead and implement that functionality.