I've got our eventPage.js file open here and what we're going to put in here is anything that we want to
run as soon as our extension loads up. So, because this eventPage.js is only going to run one time when our
extension loads, we're going to want to add any kind of listeners or event handlers in here, we're going to
want to subscribe to any events that we're interested in, and then set the callbacks so that those events
when they're triggered will call our code. So what we're going to do in this case is we want to find out
when the Chrome storage has changed, so we're just going to do this chrome.storage.onChanged.addListener.
And again, I found out about this API through the Chrome API documentation that I had shown you earlier in
module 1; you can find all of the documentation on each one of these APIs there, but what this API will do
for us is it will allow us to basically get a callback whenever anything changes in the storage for our extension.
So, we can specify a function to be called back, and in this function, we are going to get back an object
called changes, and this object is going to contain anything that's changed, and it's going to give us the
old and new values. So, let's go ahead now and utilize this to be able to set the badge text for our browser action.
So now we're going to call chrome.browserAction.setBadgeText and this particular API allows us to change
that text or basically add a badge to our browserAction, that little icon for our extension in the toolbar.
And what we're going to pass in here is basically just an object that is going to have the text that we want to set.
So we're going to have a text property and then we want to pass in a string, so we'll do changes.total,
that's going to get the total from this changes, if the total has changed this will have a value.
And then newValue is going to get the new value and we're going to have an old value and a new value for
anything that's changed, and then toString to make this a string.
So that's it; now what should happen is our event page is going to run, it's going to run this code,
which is going to add this listener, which will give us this callback for this function that's going to set
the badge text whenever anything in storage changes. We know that when something in storage changes,
it's going to be --- either our total or it's going to be our goal, so we can be pretty sure that setting
this badgeText will be the correct thing to do. Okay, so now we're going to open up our browser
and what we want to do here is we want to reload our Protein Tracker.
We need to do this because we've added that background page or event page in our manifest, so we need to
re-read this manifest. So now we should be able to go to our Protein Tracker and if we enter an amount,
let's say we add 12 more to our protein, then you can see that our badge shows up and it says 172 here,
and whatever we change this to, that badge should get updated. And if we even reset this, so if we do Reset Total,
we can see that our badge gets updated to 0.