Okay, so the last thing that we're going to do is we're going to make a context menu item to be able to
add protein by highlighting some text and then basically selecting the Add Protein Option and we're going to
utilize the event page to do this as well. So there's a couple things that we're going to need to do.
First of all, we need to be able to use the menu or to add to the menu, so we have to go back into our manifest.json,
and inside here, what we want to do is add a permission for the menu.
So we're going to do a permission here for contextMenus.
Now, we can go into our event page, and inside here, we're going to create a new menu item and then we're
going to register for an onClicked on the context menu. So let's go ahead and add this above here.
So we're going to create a variable called menuItem and we're going to set this equal to an object that
we'll create here that will have an id, which will be equal to addProtein.
This is how we'll uniquely identify our menuItem that we're going to add.
Then our menuItem will have a title, it will be called addProtein, and then it will have certain contexts
that it'll operate in, and again, you can check the API documentation to find out what all the contexts are,
but we want this to operate on selection. So this is going to basically appear on the context menu when
some text is selected on a page and only in that instance; it's not going to appear if you just right-click
without selecting anything. So now all we have to do is call chrome.contextMenus.create and we're going to
pass in our menuItem. This will make sure that our menuItem gets added to the contextMenus, but it's not
good enough just to add that, we need to create an event handler so that we can listen to any onClicked event
or any time a menuItem is clicked. So we're going to do chrome.contextMenus.onClicked.addListener.
So now we're going to specify a function that has clickData and we're going to basically execute this
function whenever a context menu item is clicked. So what we want to do here is first we want to check to
make sure this is our menu item, so we're going to say if(clickData.menuItemId == "addProtein".
So if it's our menuItem &amp;&amp;, we're going to make sure that there's actually some selection text,
so let's do clickData.selectionText. So as long as we have some text then we're good to go.
And the way that I know what's available on clickData is, again, you can check that API documentation for
the chrome APIs, and for the onClicked, it shows you what clickData has in it.
There's a bunch of different properties that you can get about the menu item.
So now what we want to do is we want to make sure that this is a number, so I'm going to actually use
the regex here; I'm just going to say intRegex. There's a lot of different ways you can check for a number,
but this is a sure way to make sure that you have a number. And then we're going to go ahead and say,
if(intRegex.test, that'll test to see if whatever we passed in here conforms to this regex, and we're going
to get clickData.selectionText. So we're actually going to get the text that's selected.
So if that is a number then what we want to do is create a variable called newTotal, but before we do that,
let's go ahead and do a get on the existing total. We're going to create some logic sort of like what we
created before when we added the amount to the total, so let's do our chrome.storage.sync.get and then we
want to get the total, and then we're going to specify our callback here, so we're going to say function(items)
and then inside here we're going to say var newTotal = 0 and then we're going to check if(items.total.
So if there is a total, then we'll go ahead and do newTotal += parseInt(items.total), so we'll go ahead
and add that to our new total. And then we can do a newTotal += parseInt(clickData.selectionText),
so we know that the selectionText is actually an integer, and if that's the case, then we can just add
that to our new total. So this is going to effectively increment our total by whatever the text that's selected,
by whatever that number is. So then we just need to save this, so we'll do chrome.storage.sync.set, and
then we'll create our object here with the total property and we'll set it equal to newTotal.
Okay, so that should be it. Now this should run when our event page runs, so we'll end up getting this
contextMenus.create, that'll create our menuItem, and then we'll subscribe to this onClicked for contextMenus.