Okay, so now let's go ahead and open up a browser window and then we're going to need to reload this.
So let's go ahead and go to our Extensions.
And since we changed the permissions, we're just going to do a reload here, and then now we should be able
to go ahead and use our context menu. Now if I right-click here, you're not going to see anything —
you're not going to see it unless I am highlighting some text and then it will have a number to use.
So let's do something like search for calorie counter.
And maybe we can find some food nutrition data, this would be a good usage for this, so let's say burger,
and we can go in here and we should be able to find something like protein, there we go, 22.3 grams.
Let's just highlight our 22 and then I can right-click here and click Add Protein and you can see the 22 appeared.
We've added 22 to our total. So this will work, I could grab, for example, this number 145, right-click,
and do Add Protein, and you can see that that total's updated here now as well.