Let's break down the steps we're going to take to create this chrome extension.
First, we'll start off by creating our Extension Directory and the manifest file for the extension.
We'll do this in a similar way as we did in the last module.
Then, we'll design the main UI for the popup when a user clicks the Extensions icon from the toolbar.
This UI will have a current total and goal displayed,
as well as give the user a place to add a protein amount to the total.
Next, we'll add the ability to actually save the total and display the correct total in the popup UI.
We'll utilize the Chrome Storage APIs to save and retrieve the saved data.
After that, we'll create an options page for our extension. The options page will show the current goal
and let the user change the goal and save it or reset the current protein total.
Then, we'll add some notifications to the extension; we'll do this by using the Chrome Notifications API,
which allows us to pop up a small notification at the bottom of the screen.
We'll add a notification for when the user resets the total and also one for when they have met their goal.
After that, we'll use the Chrome Browser Action API to add a badge to our Extension icon that will display
the current protein total. In order to do this, we'll need to register for any changes to the protein total,
and since we want this functionality to work regardless of how the total is updated, we'll use an event page
to implement this functionality. Finally, we'll use our event page again to register a context menu item
that will allow a user to add protein just by selecting a number on a page and right-clicking, then choosing Add Protein.
That's it; quite a bit of functionality in this extension, but it's actually
pretty easy to implement using the chrome APIs, as you'll see coming up next.