So the first thing that we're going to do is we're going to create our directory that we're going to create
our extension in, so I'm just going to create this directory called ProteinTracker, and inside here we're
going to create our manifest file. So I'm just going to add a new text document and I'm just going to call this
manifest.json and we're going to create this file just like we did for our first Hello World extension;
I'm just going to go ahead and open this up in Visual Studio.
And like I said, you can use whatever editor that you want and what we're going to do is we're just going
to go ahead and set all the properties for this manifest file. So remember, there are a few things that
we need to have - we need to have the manifest_version and this is going to be version 2 because that's
the current version of the manifest, the latest version, and then we want to give this a name, which we'll
have to specify, so we're going to call this Protein Tracker, and then let's go ahead and add a description.
This one is optional, but we want to have a description, so let's say "Tracks a user's protein totals
throughout the day." Then we're going to want the version for our actual extension, which we're just going
to make this 1.0 to start with, and now we're going to want to add our browser action, because remember
this is of type browser_action. In the next module we'll be creating a page_action one, but in this one
we are using a browser_action, which means that it's going to show up in that toolbar always.
And with this browser_action, we're creating a new object inside here, a nested object, so you can think of
these as sort of subproperties. So we have our default_icon and we're just going to call this icon.png,
just like we did before, and then for our default_popup, we're going to do the same thing as well and we're
just going to call this popup.html. And that's all we're going to do for our manifest at this point.
We'll be adding some things later to this manifest when we need to add some permissions and an options page
and our background page, but for now that's all we'll need.