So next we're going to go ahead and create our
user interface, our basic popup.html, so we're just going to create a ‘New Text Document' and we're just
going to call this popup.html and we're going to go ahead and open this one up in Visual Studio to edit it
and what we want to do here is design the user interface for our main popup, so this will be when you click
the icon for our extension, it should show this UI. We're just going to make a real simple user interface.
You could, of course, make something more complicated if you want to, but we're just going to create an HTML document
with our doctype html and then inside here, of course, we have our html and then our head and then our body.
And what we're going to put inside here is we're just going to put in h1, that will say Protein Tracker,
and then we'll add some h2's for everything else we're going to have in here.
So let's have a total and then let's make a span here so that we can actually set this total to some value,
so we're going to give this an id of total and we're going to set it to 0 by default.
We'll do the same thing here for the goal, so we'll put Goal, and then we're going to add an h3 for ‘Enter amount.'
So we'll say Enter amount and then we want to have an input that we'll call amount and this will be of type text.
So that will let us have our little text input there and then we want a button for someone to go ahead and
submit this to enter the values, so we're just going to make this addAmount and we're going to make the type
equal to submit and then the value, this'll be what it says, it'll say Add Protein.
Okay, and then we want to go ahead and add a title, this'll actually end up being a tool tip for our extension
when you hover over it, so we'll call this Protein Tracker, and we're going to add some script files,
but we're not going to add those yet, we're just going to leave this as is, and remember that little trick
that I showed you in the last module - we can use that here to look at our user interface.
In fact, I found that if you have two monitors, you can actually leave this open on one and then make your
edits in your HTML and you'll see them change here automatically, so this is kind of a quick way to do a
preview of your HTML and the nice thing about this is it works regardless of what editor you're using.
So we have a real simple user interface; the basic idea here is that we're going to have the Total here
that we can swap out, the Goal that we can swap out, the user should be able to enter some amount, and
then be able to click this Add Protein, and it will make it so that it adds that amount to the total.