So at this point we're almost ready to go ahead and test out our extension to get it loaded into our browser,
but before we do that we do need an icon, so I've already created an icon here, a very nice looking icon
that says PT for protein tracker and this icon, remember, this is 19x19 pixels — this is the icon that's
going to be displayed in that toolbar. So now we should be all set up to actually add this extension.
So I'm just going to go ahead and get a browser window here and then I'm just going to go to Settings and
Extensions, that's another way to get to Extensions if you forget the URL up here, and then we're going to
go ahead and do a ‘Load unpacked extension' and we're just going to find where this extension is.
So it's under here, Creating Chrome Extension, and then I've got this ProteinTracker.
So now you can see that it immediately loaded up, we've got our nice little icon here, and then when we
click it, we see our user interface; it just says Protein Tracker, Total: 0, Goal: 0, Enter amount —
of course this doesn't work quite yet, but you should get to this step if you have everything set up correctly.
You have to have your icon, you have to have the HTML. If you reference anything that doesn't exist,
you'll have a problem loading this, so that's why we haven't referenced anything else in our manifest or in our HTML yet.