Okay, so now it's time to actually implement this functionality to be able to actually add some protein and
to save that data, but before we can do that, we're going to need to go ahead and create our JavaScript files
and bring in our jQuery. So what I'm going to do here is I'm going to link to our JavaScript and then we'll
create that JavaScript file, so we're just going to say script src = and we're just going to call this popup.js
and then we're also going to want to link our jQuery, so let's do a script src = jQuery and let me go ahead
and copy this entire string. Okay, so now we'll need to add these to our directory.
So let's go ahead and go to our directory and I'm going to go ahead and just copy the jQuery instance that
we already downloaded before, so I've got the jQuery file already, and then we're just going to create a new file
and we're going to just call this popup.js and then we'll need to go ahead and edit this and then create
that functionality.