Okay, so I'm here in the popup.js in the Editor and what we want to do here is we want to make it so that
that click button does something, so that's the first thing that we're going to do is we're just going to
test this to make sure it works. I'm just going to use an alert to show an alert box that shows that we've
hooked up this click. So, we're just going to do our jQuery $(function, to have this function start or run
when the page loads up, and then inside here we're going to hook up our event handler, so we're just going
to do #addAmount and we're going to say when it's clicked, execute the following function, and inside here,
all we're going to do for now is just we're going to say alert(‘clicked').
So now we just want to verify that this is going to work, so I'm just going to go ahead and
open up a browser window and I'm just going to click this and then click the Add Protein button.
You can see that it says clicked, so we know that we're hooked up correctly.
You always want to take these small steps whenever you're doing something like this because you don't want
to end up putting a lot of code in here and then trying to debug that; by doing this really small step,
I know that this popup.js is being loaded and that it's hooking up to this click and everything is working.
So now I'm ready to take the next step.