Hi, this is John Sonmez from Pluralsight, and in this module I'll be showing you how to create a Page Action Extension.
So far we've created two browser action extensions, and while browser action extensions are useful,
we don't always need our extension to be available on every page we visit in Chrome.
By creating an extension that uses a page action instead of the browser action, we can create extensions
that are more tailored to specific content on web pages or specific web pages that will be displayed and add
functionality conditionally. This is a very powerful way to build chrome extensions, because it allows us
to create extensions that aren't always taking up space on the toolbar and are able to show up at the right time
to do something useful. I'll also be showing you how to use content scripts, which are another powerful
tool in the Chrome Extensions toolbox that allows us to actually inject JavaScript in CSS into an active page
to change it however we like. By the end of this module, you should be able to create your own
page action-based extension, understand how to pass messages, and utilize content scripts.