Okay, so let's go ahead and add a content script to our extension.
So what we're going to do is we're basically just going to add here a section for any content scripts.
So we're just going to call this content_scripts and then inside here we're going to add an array of the
content_scripts that are going to be added. Each one is going to be a particular object, so let's go
ahead and add an object here, and then we're going to want to have a matches property, so we're going to
specify what this should match, and I'm just going to copy this.
We're going to use a couple of the Pluralsight URLs that have some course lists here.
We don't want this to show up on every single page in Pluralsight and we don't want this to show up on
non-Pluralsight pages, so we're going to say basically anything under this training/Courses/* -
this * is a wild card, which means that it'll match anything that starts with this, and then anything under
this URL as well, and you can match your wild cards on a couple of different things.
You can check out the wild card matching if you look at the content_scripts in the chrome documentation for extensions.
It has a few other ways that you can use to match them, but most often you'll probably use matching similar
to how we're doing it here. So, next we're going to specify what our JavaScript is, so we're going to say
js and then here we have an array of our JavaScript. So, what we're going to include here is a JavaScript file
that we're going to call Pluralsight_cs (for content script) .js and then we're actually going to add our
jQuery as well, because we want to have that accessible from our content script, so we want to make sure
that we include this. Whenever you use content_scripts, if you have some library that you're going to use,
you might want to include it here because you can't always rely on that being on our page.
So instead of us relying on this version of jQuery existing on the page, we're going to make sure that we
include it here, and we'll go ahead and add a comma after this, so now our manifest file should be complete.