Okay, so now let's go ahead and actually add our content script.
So we're just going to go ahead and go to our directory here.
And we're going to create a file, so let's do a ‘New Text Document' and we're going to call this Pluralsight_cs.js.
Now we're going to go ahead and
open this up, and by the way with our content script, if it's going to run on Pluralsight, we do have to
add a permission for this as well in order to be able to give our extension permission to operate on any
of those sites that we want to use this from. So let's go ahead and do that real quick before we actually
implement our content script. So all we're going to do is we're going to give it a general permission for
Pluralsight, so we're just going to add here http://Pluralsight.com/*, so that'll make sure that it has
permission for anything it needs to do on Pluralsight.
Now inside here, what we actually want to do is we're going to want to basically send a message to our
eventPage that's going to tell it to go ahead and display the page_action.
All this at this point is just to get the page action being displayed correctly.
Now remember, our content script is going to run on these particular pages, so it's going to immediately run
this JavaScript, and what we're going to do by doing this is make sure that our page_action only shows up
when we're at one of these URLs or a URL that matches one of these.
So, we're going to go into our Pluralsight_cs.js and here what we want to do is basically just send a message
that says to show. Okay, so what we're going to do inside here is we're just going to do chrome.runtime.sendMessage
and then here we can send a message and it can basically be any object.
So we're just going to create an object that we're going to have a property called action on and we're going
to set the action equal to show. You could do whatever kind of format you wanted in order to make this work.
I'm just going to use this so that we'll have some convention of we're going to check what the action is,
the action is going to say what that particular action should be, so we're basically just sending this show message.
Now remember, this script is going to run on any page that matches this matches here.
So, as soon as this runs, it's going to be sending this message that's going to say show.
Then on our eventPage, we want to go ahead and receive this message and check for that show action.
If it's a show, then we're going to go head and actually show it — we don't want to show this always.
So instead of just executing this code, we're going to change this now and we're going to say,
chrome.runtime.onMessage, addListener, so this is going to add a listener for us, and this is going to take
a function, this will be our callback, which will give us the request, it'll give us the sender, and we can
send a response. Now we won't actually need to send a response in our case, so then we're going to go ahead
and actually put this all inside here and we want to check to see if the request.action is equal to show
before we do anything, and then let's go ahead and end this correctly.
Okay, so now let's talk real quick about what's going to happen here.
So, we're going to load up a page; when we load up that page, if it matches here, it's going to run
these two scripts — this Pluralsight one and this jQuery one.
This Pluralsight one, if it runs, it will send a message that has an action set to show and then this
eventPage has already registered to receive any messages. So any messages that come through it's going to
receive, it's going to check to see if it gets show, and if it does then it's going to figure out what
the currentWindow, current activeTab is, and it's going to show the pageAction for that.