Okay, so it's time to test this out. Let's go ahead and reload our Pluralsight Helper.
You can see we don't have a pageAction here, so that's good.
I'm going to go to Pluralsight.com; I still don't see a pageAction — that's good.
If I go to the Top 100 Leaderboard, there we go, we've got our pageAction, so it's just showing up when
we're on those pages that match what that content script said. So, now if I go, for example, to let's say
the blog, we don't see anything show up here, but if I were to go to
an author page, let's go to Shawn Wildermuth, and now you can see that this shows up again.
So a little tricky to get this working. We have a little bit of an indirection here, because we don't have
the ability to really just have the matches for the pageAction itself and we need a way to display the
pageAction, so we have to basically have a content script, that content script has to send a message to our
eventPage, which is listening, which can then actually execute script that will show our pageAction inside
of the correct tab, but once you have that framework in place, now it's pretty easy.
Now we have access to be able to send messages from our content page to the rest of our extension and
next we're going to make that go the opposite direction when we actually implement functionality.
So we're going to make it so when we click these buttons that it's actually going to send a message
the other way to the actual content script.