Okay, now before we move on, I did want to show you one more thing that you can do with content_scripts
that's actually pretty useful. You can add CSS to style something with the content script; in fact,
you can basically make an extension that just restyles some web page if you want.
In fact, there are extensions that already do that. So all we have to do is we're just going to create
a CSS file, so we're just going to create this Pluralsight_cs.css, and let's go ahead and edit this.
And we're just going to make this make the author name bold and a little bit larger so it'll be easier to see.
That should be pretty clear that our style is working if we see that on the author pages or the course list pages.
So we're going to say font-weight is equal to bolder and then we're just going to do font-size: large.
I'll go ahead and save this, we'll go to our manifest, and what we're going to do inside here is we're going
to add CSS. So we can just put a comma here and then add CSS to this and then this is just going to take an
array of CSS pages - we just have the one, which is Pluralsight_cs.css, and now if we go ahead and save this
and we go to our Extensions;
we'll go ahead and reload this Pluralsight Helper, and now if I go to Pluralsight and I go to, let's say,
the Top 100 Leaderboard, you can see that the author names are now bold, and they're large.
So I'm basically applying the style automatically to this page and anything that matches this,
so you can see, of course, our UI is showing up here for our pageAction, but this is really, really useful
to just be able to restyle something. In fact, you can take an existing website, maybe you don't like the
way that it looks, and just create an extension that adds your own custom style to it, and it might actually
be useful to other people who are using that website as well.