Okay, so the next thing that we're going to do is we're going to go ahead and implement our functionality;
we're going to make it so that when a user clicks on that page action, that show course count, it's going
to actually show the count of the number of courses on that page for an author next to the author's name,
so it's going to add them up and show that. So in order to do that, what we're going to do is we're going
to hook up in our popup.html this courseCounts button. We're going to make it actually send a message to
the correct tab to that content script, and then that content script that's running on that page is going
to go ahead and execute some JavaScript that will go ahead and modify that page and show those courseCounts.
So, let's go ahead and create this popup.js; we're just going to be using jQuery like we did before.
So we're just going to do our function here and then we need to go ahead and setup our handler, so we're
going to do (‘#courseCounts').click and that should match this courseCounts here - let's just double check.
Okay, and then we want to give the function here that it's going to call, and for this function, what we're
going to want to do is the same thing that we had done before. So I'm just going to actually copy this in
order to query all of our tabs. So, we're just going to do chrome.tabs.query, look for the active and current one.
Now we need to do this because we have to send a message to a specific tab, we want to send it to whatever
the current tab is, because remember, content_scripts could be running on multiple tabs, we could have
multiple content_scripts running, so we have to know what tab we're sending this to.
We're going to send it to the active one. So now we're going to actually call chrome.tabs.sendMessage and
this is how we send a message to a tab and we want to send it to tabs, the 0 with index — that'll give us the id,
and then we're going to do action: "courseCounts", and I do want to point out here that you can pass
whatever object you want. I just happened to be creating an object that has a property action that has
the value of what the action is, but I'm just using that for convention; it doesn't matter what you pass here,
whatever message you want to pass you can pass, and however you want to do your messaging - it's basically
open to however you want to use this. So let's go ahead and save this.
And now what's going to happen is when we show our user interface for our popup.html for that pageAction,
it's going to go ahead and execute this JavaScript for a popup.js, which will basically hook up to that click.
So when someone clicks that button in the UI, it's going to go ahead and figure out what the active tab is
and then send this courseCounts a message.