Okay, so the next thing that we'll need to do is to actually
make it so that our content_scripts has a listener to be able to receive the message.
So we're going to go back into our content script and remember we were just sending this message before,
but now we're actually going to do this chrome.runtime.onMessage.addListener, so this will make sure that
we're listening for messages, and then we're going to have a callback — that'll be a function that takes
a request and then a sender and then a sendResponse. Then inside here, we're just going to check to see
what the message was, so we're going to say if(request.action == "courseCounts", then that's the one that we
want to handle, so we will do something with this message. So we're going to actually implement the
functionality to add up the courses per author and go ahead and change the DOM or change the HTML that's in
that page to show the courseCounts next to the author name. Now I'm just going to copy some code that I had
written before to do this and we're not going to go over this code, because this isn't really important to
creating the extension, but it basically just goes through, finds out all the authors, it creates this map,
and counts up each one of the courses, and then it's going to go ahead and modify the actual DOM to display
the author name followed by the course count. Okay, so let's go ahead and test this out next.