Okay, so now we should be able to go over here and reload our extension.
So we're just going to go into Extensions and Pluralsight Helper, and now if we go to Pluralsight,
and we go to, let's say the
Top 100 Leaderboard, we can see that our CSS is being applied, we've got our pageAction, but if I click this
‘Add course counts', now you can see that instantly I have basically gotten all of the counts for each
author so we can see how many courses that they have on the Top 100.
And you can see here that Scott Allen is still dominating the Top 100 with 14 courses up there,
so this is pretty neat; we can actually apply this to the new releases page as well.
And this has actually all the courses that have been released on Pluralsight from day one, so it's pretty
interesting if we do this one. We can get the courseCounts for every single author, so you can see
how many courses each author has done, what their total number of courses is.
And just to recap real quick what's happening when we're doing this is, when we click this button here this
‘Add course counts', it's basically figuring out what the active tab is, it's sending a message to the
content script here, so this content script receives the message, and then it executes the JavaScript that's
going to manipulate this page. Our actual UI here, the JavaScript behind this, can't manipulate the page
directly; it's not even really attached directly to a page, it's attached to our extension to our actual
pageAction, so we have to use this indirection, we have to use the message passing in order to be able to
get access to the actual page.