Now the last thing we're going to implement for our plug-in is to make it so
that this table here is sortable when we click this ‘Make sortable' button.
Now rather than reinventing the wheel, we're actually going to use a jQuery plug-in called DataTables.
So we can go to jQuery datatable and here you can see there's this DataTables plug-in for jQuery.
I'm just going to use this as an example of how you could use a plug-in or use something else in your content scripts.
So what we're going to do is we're just going to download this,
and then we're going to go ahead and get the JavaScript file out of here.
So inside here, you'll find underneath the media there's a js and then here there's this jquery.dataTable.js.
So we're just going to go ahead and add that to our extension, we'll just drop it in here, and then what
we're going to do is modify our manifest file to include this. So we can just go to our Editor and then
in our manifest here we can add for our js for our content_scripts, this data table, so we're just going
to add this one and let's go ahead and copy this so we get the right name.
Okay, so now what's going to happen is that any of the pages that load our content_scripts are also going
to load this jQuery.dataTables.js, which is going to give us the ability to very easily convert a regular
table into a sortable table.