Okay, so now let's go ahead and implement the functionality.
We're going to do this in a very similar way as how we did the previous one, so we're going to make this
makeSortable button work. We're just going to go to our popup.js, and inside here, we're basically going to
do the same thing, so I'm just going to copy this and paste this, and we want to make sure that we have
the right id, it's makeSortable, so I'm going to copy here and paste this in here.
So now when makeSortable is clicked, what we're going to do is we're going to send a message, except instead
of sending the message courseCounts, we're going to send the message makeSortable.
I'll go ahead and save that, and then on the other end we need to receive this message.
So if we go to our content script, so this Pluralsight_cs, we'll go ahead and go there, here we're going to
check for the other request.action, we're going to check to see if we have makeSortable, right now we're
just checking for course count. So we'll go ahead and put another if here, so we'll just say,
if(request.action == "makeSortable", then we're going to go ahead and make the table sortable.
And the way that we're going to do this is we're going to grab the table; this table happens to have a class
with the name course, so we're just going to check for this .course, which will give us our table,
and then all we have to do with this jQuery plug-in for data table is just say dataTable, it's basically
adding this method to the table class, and we can pass in some parameters as an object.
And so we're just going to pass in this bPaginate and set it equal to false and what this will do is it'll
make sure that it doesn't page our results; otherwise, it's going to page our results.
We don't want them paged because we want to use the actual paging that's already in the Pluralsight pages;
we don't want to page this by 10 rows, otherwise we won't get all the rows that exist.
And that's it, that's how simple it is to add this functionality.
All we're doing here really is we're just basically modifying the page, we're running this script from this message.
So now we can go ahead and test this out.