Okay, so let's go ahead and reload our extension just to make sure that it is up-to-date.
So we'll just reload this, and now if we go to, let's say, the Pluralsight New Releases page, and then we
click on our page_action, we can click this ‘Make sortable' and you can see it's actually modified this
table and now all of these columns are sortable, so we could actually sort by author, and now you can see
that it's sorted alphabetically by author. We can still even add our courseCounts, so now we can see the
actual courses that each author has done all on this single page.
We can find out some interesting information, like what is the longest and shortest course.
We can sort by duration here, so we can see that the shortest course is IronRuby by Example, and then if I
were to sort the other way, the longest course is this Design Patterns Library and then Advanced BizTalk Server 2010.
You can also sort by release date or the level. So, this is a pretty useful functionality that we've
been able to add very easily. We can also do this on the popular,
so on the Top 100 Leaderboard we could sort by author here just by activating this to make sortable,
and now we have that functionality. So you can imagine, there's quite a few different things that you could use this for.
You could create all kinds of functionality for different web pages and extend them with a chrome extension.
Instead of trying to modify the web page or do something else, you can basically just add on and add your
own code and add your own functionality and features. This is a really useful way to be able to utilize
something that someone else has created and be able to add functionality to it without having to reimplement it.