As a Pluralsight author, I've often found the need to be able to get a count of how many courses authors
have produced and sort some of the course data from the Pluralsight website.
I like to see how well my courses are doing in the Top 100 and be able to see things like, what the longest
courses in the library are or the shortest ones. I've always thought it would be nice if I could see
the number of courses that an author has in the Top 100 or overall how many courses they've produced next
to the author name, and I've also wanted to be able to sort the columns in the table that displays the courses.
We're going to be building a chrome extension that will allow us to do both of those things.
We'll be creating an extension that will add a little icon like the one you can see here in the address
bar whenever there is a Pluralsight page that has course content.
We'll then be able to click that icon to see a list of helper commands we can run on the page.
I think you'll be pleasantly surprised at just how easy it is to get this working.