We talked briefly about page actions in the first module, but I wanted to go over them one more time here
now that we have seen browser actions and can better understand the difference between the two.
As you can see here, a page action, unlike a browser action, shows up in the address bar and it isn't always there.
In fact, by default, the page action doesn't show up at all; you have to explicitly call into the Chrome API
to tell Chrome to show a page action. This is the key difference between the two.
Other than that, the only major difference is that a page action can't have a badge like we had added to
the Protein Tracker to show the total protein count. We can create a UI for the page action, just like
we could for a browser action, as you can see here. When creating a chrome extension, it's important to
realize when it makes sense to use a page action instead of a browser action.
It is best to make an extension that only works in a subset of pages or websites, a page action in most cases,
because it doesn't end up taking a valuable screen real-estate in the toolbar when it isn't needed.