Okay, let's go ahead and get started. We're going to start just like we did with the other extensions by
creating our extension directory first. So what I'm going to do is I'm going to create a new directory here
called PluralsightHelper. And inside here, we're going to start off by creating our manifest file.
So, we're just going to do a ‘New Text Document' and we'll call this manifest.json.
Okay, and we'll go ahead and open this up; I'm just going to edit this in Visual Studio.
Like I said, you can use whatever editor that you want, and we're just going to create our manifest file
just like we've done before. And remember that we want to start with our manifest_version, which is 2,
and then we're going to want to add our name here, so the name for this one, we're going to call this
Pluralsight Helper, and then we want to have a description and we'll just make this say "Adds functionality
to the Pluralsight website." And don't forget your commas. And then we're going to say that this is
version 1.0 of our extension. Okay, now we're just going to start off by creating a page action,
so I'm just going to go ahead and add this page action section right now to our manifest, so we're going to say,
page_action, and we're going to do this instead of that browser action.
We can't have a page action and a browser action; obviously for an extension it has to be in one place or the other.
So then we're going to put in our default_icon and we'll just call this icon.png; I've already created an
icon that we can use here, and then we're going to put a default_title in here; this'll be just a title of this page action,
which will be Pluralsight Helper. Then we're going to add a default popup, so we're going to say,
default_popup, and this works just like it did for the browser action; we're just going to call this popup.html.