So next we're going to go ahead and create our popup.html.
I'm just going to go ahead and create a file here and we'll just call this popup.html and we're just going
to create our user interface, we're just going to make a really, really simple user interface, just like we did
for our browser_action. So let's go ahead and put our doctype html in here and then add our html and then
we'll add a head tag and we want to have a body tag. And inside our head, we'll just go ahead and put the title,
which we'll call this Pluralsight Helper, and then for our script we're going to add jQuery just like we did before.
Let me go ahead and copy this to get the exact name and we'll need to copy jQuery, of course, into our plug-in directory
and then we're going to have another script, which will be our script for this page, which we'll just call
popup.js, just like we did for the other extensions. And inside the body, we'll just put an h1 that says,
Pluralsight Helper Options, and then let's add two buttons; we're just going to make one button with the id
of courseCounts — this we'll use for our course counts, this will be a submit button, and we'll give it a
value of "Add course counts" and then let's go ahead and copy this and we'll add a second button,
which will be called makeSortable, in order to make the table sortable, and we'll call this "Make sortable."
So that's it, just a very simple user interface; remember, this user interface is going to be displayed when
we actually click on that page action. Now, when we first set up this extension, we're not going to see the
page action; we're going to go ahead and install the extension at this point to make sure that our manifest
file is correct and that everything is correct next, but before we could do that we do need to create this
popup.js and make sure our jQuery is in the directory. So let's go ahead and do that real quick.
We're just going to do a ‘New Text Document' and we'll just make a popup.js and we're not going to put
anything in there yet and then we're going to go ahead and copy jQuery into our directory.