Okay, so now let's go ahead and load this extension into Chrome.
We do need one last thing before we do this — we need to copy our icon in here.
I just went ahead and created this icon, it's just a little Pluralsight icon with a plus here to indicate
it's Pluralsight Helper, and so now that we have that, we can go ahead and do this ‘Load unpacked extension'
and then we're going to look for our extension, which is Pluralsight Helper, click OK, and we should see
Pluralsight Helper is showing up in here. Now, we're not going to see anything at this point,
because remember, unlike a browser action that shows up automatically inside here, a page action is going to
show up right here at the end of this address bar, but it's only going to show up when we actually show it.
So we actually have to implement some JavaScript that's going to tell Chrome to show this; otherwise,
we're not going to actually even see anything from our extension at this point.