Now to go ahead and display our page action, we're going to start off by just creating an event page,
just like we did with the last extension, and this event page is just going to contain the JavaScript
to just show the page action. Now it's going to show it on every page by default, because it's just going
to run for every page, but when we actually create our content script, we're going to make the content script
be responsible for telling the event page to go ahead and show it and then it will only show it for the
Pluralsight website, but we're just going to do this to get started.
So, we're going to go ahead and create a new document, we're going to call this eventPage.js, and then
we're going to go ahead and go into our manifest file
and we want to add this event page. We're going to do this just like we did for the previous extension we created,
so we're just going to say background, and then inside here we go ahead and put in our scripts.
So we're going to add scripts and then we have an array of scripts and we're just going to have the one
eventPage.js, and then we want to tell this to be persistent false so that we don't have a background page;
instead, we're going to have an eventPage, so persistent false.
Okay, so now let's go ahead and modify our eventPage.
We're going to go ahead and drag it into the Editor and what we want to do in this eventPage is we want to
basically just show our pageAction. So the way that we do that is we just do chrome.pageAction.show and
then we're going to specify what the tabId is. Now we don't know what the tabId is so we have to figure out
what tab to show this on. So, instead of just doing chrome.pageAction.show, let's go ahead and comment this out,
what we're going to do is we're going to do chrome.tabs.query and this is going to let us query the tabs
based on some conditions, so we're going to say active equals true.
We want basically the active tab and we want it to be in the current window, so we're going to say,
currentWindow: true, as well. And then we can pass back a function that's going to be executed with the
tabs passed in as a parameter, it'll be a callback here. So here's our function, so then once we have this,
now we can go ahead and paste this in here and we're just going to say chrome.pageAction.show and we can get
our tabId by doing tabs
This should really only be 1, because there's only going to be one active tab for the current window.
Okay, then let's go ahead and close this out, put a semicolon here, and now we should be set to go.
Okay, now we're going to need to reload this in our browser to actually see this show up, so we're just going to
first add some permissions to our manifest.json in order to make sure that we can actually manipulate the tabs,
which is what we're basically doing when we're doing that query on the tabs, and we're going to be showing
our page_action. So we're just going to do a permissions and we're just going to add one permission here,
which is tabs. Now we'll go ahead and save this.
Let's open up our browser and I'm going to go ahead and enable my Pluralsight Helper extension.
So when I enable this, it should reload, I'll just reload this one time to be sure, and you can see that our
page_action is showing up, and it doesn't actually do anything at this point and it's only going to show up on this page.
It's basically showing up when that eventPage runs; remember, we only have one eventPage, so it's going to
run wherever this first gets loaded. Since it's on this Chrome extensions page it's going to load up here.
If we go somewhere else or open a new window, it doesn't show up, but we are going to make this work for
multiple pages, or actually, the correct pages, once we add our content script - we'll need that in order to
be able to make this more conditional. If you wanted, however, you could make it so that, for example,
your eventPage hooked into some event, like whenever a page loaded, and then maybe it checked on that page
for some certain text, and based on some text, it triggered showing this page_action.