We've already briefly mentioned Content Scripts, but let's dive a little deeper now that we have more of
an understanding of how extensions work in Chrome. Up till this point, everything we've done as an extension
has worked at a high level. Nothing we created so far actually manipulated an actual web page and its data.
In fact, using browser actions, page actions, and even background pages and event pages, we can't actually
do much to a page itself. In order to actually manipulate a loaded page with our extension, we need to use
a content script. Content scripts are registered in the manifest file and include a Matches property to
determine what pages the content scripts will run on. Most often this is a URL with a wild card.
For example, with our extension, we'll be running our content scripts on certain Pluralsight URLs.
The content script itself can be JavaScript or CSS. You can really think of the content script as being
some additional JavaScript or CSS that's run when a certain page loads.
Content scripts basically get tacked onto a loaded page and can operate on those pages like any other script or CSS,
but content scripts can't actually utilize most of the functionality of the chrome APIs available to other
parts of an extension; they have to pass messages to get their work done, which we'll talk about next.