Content scripts do not have the ability to directly communicate with Background Pages or UI Pages or most of
the other chrome APIs. In order for a content script to be able to do something like show a page action,
for instance, or update a badge count, the content script has to use the chrome message API to send a message
that another part of the extension is listening for. Most commonly, you'll use this messaging API to send
single messages to and from content script using the chrome.runtime.sendMessage and
chrome.tabs.sendMessageMethods, but Chrome also supports long-lived connections using ports,
passing messages to other extensions, sending messages from web pages, and even messaging with native applications.
In this course, we'll just be using the simple and most used approach of sending messages to and from
content scripts though. We'll be using messaging to both send a message from the content script to the
event page to tell it to display the page action and from the page action UI to the content script to tell
it to make modifications to the page.