Hi, this is John Sonmez from Pluralsight and welcome to this course on Creating Chrome Extensions.
Chrome extensions are a useful way to add functionality to the Chrome web browser which can come in handy
in a variety of different contexts. You can use Chrome extensions to integrate capabilities of your application
or service directly into Chrome or you can create Chrome extensions that add useful functionality to Chrome itself
and even modify web pages browsed with Chrome on the fly. In this course I'll take you through the surprisingly
easy process of creating Chrome extensions. We'll learn the basics about Chrome extensions and how they work.
And create our own extensions. We'll create both an extension that uses a user interface and one that works in the
background to add capabilities to webpages in the browser. So, if you've always wanted to create
Chrome extensions, but you didn't know where to get started, or you thought it might be too hard,
keep watching and I'll show you just how easy it is.