Chrome extensions can be generally broken up into three main parts.
A background page, UI pages, and content scripts. Let's talk about each one of these important components
in a little more detail.
First we have background pages. A Chrome extensions can have a background page which is basically an HTML page
that runs in the background. Typically, a background page will have some JavaScript code in it
that will be used to control the capabilities of the extension when it's active from the Chrome UI.
You can actually see a list of the background pages running from Chrome using the Chrome Task Manager
as you can see here. Background pages can either be persistent or event pages.
Persistence background pages are always running in open.
This can be necessary when you have a background page that stores some persistent state for your extensions
or handles some long running process to manage a task. But, background pages can be resource hogs so they
should be used carefully. Often a better approach is to use an event page which is only loaded when it's needed.
Event pages work just like background pages, except that they don't persist themselves all the time.
Instead, an event page is registered for a specific event which will trigger it and cause it to become active.