So, I want to show you how you can check out the background pages that are running inside of Chrome.
And also, just another tool that you can utilize when you're developing your extensions that you'll
probably find useful for checking the memory requirements and seeing what's running.
So, if you go to your Chrome options here and then go to tools, you can see this Task Manager.
Now this shows you more than just the background pages.
It shows you your actual browser and the tabs and then any apps that are running.
And also, your extensions themselves and how much memory they're taking up.
This is pretty useful information. But you can also see here something's like the background page if you have
different background pages running. And you can see how much memory those background pages are taking.
So, this is really useful for figuring out exactly what's going on.
And it shows you which background pages are running. So, if you're wondering why your browser's running so slow,
or why it's taking up so much memory, when you look in here and you see how many extensions are actually
taking up a large amount of memory, that's your answer.
So the more extensions that you install, the more that you're going to be using up memory with Chrome.
And you want to be careful with that when you create your own extension; you probably want to look in here
and check out the memory requirements of that extension. Especially if you're using a background page,
you can see that some background pages can take up quite a bit of memory.
In fact, I have a background page for this REST console, and it doesn't even really make sense.
I'm not using the REST console activity, so it might make sense to disable this extension.
This extension probably really doesn't need a background page because I can't imagine why it's using one
at this point when I'm not even using the REST console in my browser.