Content scripts are scripts that are executed when certain pages load in the browser.
These scripts can be used to essentially inject JavaScript into a page to modify its behavior or user interface.
The content script essentially becomes part of the page that was loaded.
This means a content script is going to behave like any other script on the page.
So, content scripts can't directly modify the DOM of the HTML pages packaged with the extension,
like UI pages and background pages can. But, content scripts can send messages back to the parent extension
to ask pages in the paired extension to modify a UI page or perform some extension-related functionality.
Likewise, a background page or UI page can send a message to a content script to cause it to perform an action
on the page it's running on. We'll look more at content scripts when we utilize them to implement an
extension in Module 4.