So now you should have the basic knowledge about Chrome extensions needed to create our own extensions.
Chrome extensions are basically just a collection of HTML, CSS, and JavaScript packaged with a manifest file
that tells Chrome how to integrate their functionality into the browser.
But, as we talked about in this module, extensions are pretty powerful and can utilize the Chrome APIs to
control and manipulate many aspects of the browser. We also talked about the three parts of the
Chrome extension; the background pages, UI pages, and content scripts.
But we'll be looking more in depth into each of these as we utilize them and some of the extensions we'll
be creating later in this course. Up next, we'll be creating a very basic Hello World extension to see how
all the technology of a Chrome extension works and get you familiar with working with extensions before we
get into the details of the Chrome API or the JavaScript code used to interact with it.
Thanks for joining me and take care.