One of the nice things about Chrome extensions is that they're actually very easy to create.
Chrome extensions are made using web technologies you're already probably familiar with like, HTML, CSS,
and JavaScript. That means that just about anyone with some basic web skills, regardless of their primary
programing language background, or choice of technology stack, can learn to create Chrome extensions.
You'll need to be at least somewhat familiar with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to get the most out of this
course though, since we won't be covering the basics here. Other than that small requirement,
this course is basically for everyone. It doesn't matter if you're a .NET developer or Java developer or
even prefer Ruby or Python. Since Chrome extensions only use the web technologies, everything in this course
will apply equally well. Another benefit of Chrome's easy to create extensions are that you can learn to
create extensions for a variety of different reasons. Unlike some technologies that require deep
understanding of a framework and lots of study. The simplicity of this topic opens up the possibility of
creating Chrome extensions for just even personal use. Plus, as an added bonus, you'll look like a genius
when you show your boss the Chrome extensions you made over the weekend for your specific software.