This course is broken up into five modules which will take us through the basics, the creation of
three Chrome extensions, and then finally, the important issues of debugging in deployment.
We'll start with the first module which you're currently watching in which we'll discuss the basics of
Chrome extensions and how they work. And discover just how much you can actually do with some simple
JavaScript code thanks to Chrome's extensive APIs.
Then in Module 2, we'll create our first extension. This extension won't do much, it'll be a basic
Hello World extension, but it will give us a chance to go over the basics of the mechanical process
of creating an extension and learn how the different technologies and pieces fit together to
create the final Chrome extension bundle. This module should help you gain the confidence that creating an
actual extension itself is pretty easy.
Once we have created a basic extension, it'll be time to do something a little more useful.
In Module 3 we'll create a browser action extension which is just an extension that will give an icon
in the browser that can be clicked to display a UI. You've probably seen many of these types of extensions
before because they are the most common and most obvious types of extensions.
Then in Module 4 we'll create a page action extension. This kind of extension runs in the back ground and
modifies a web page by adding capabilities to it. It isn't as prominent as a browser action extension,
but it is a very powerful capability of Chrome extensions that can do some pretty awesome things.
In Module 5 we'll learn two important things about Chrome extensions.
First, how to debug them using the Chrome developer tools, and then how to deploy them.
We'll see how we can package up a Chrome extension and submit it to the Chrome Web Store so that
others can download it and make use of it.