Let's start off by talking about what exactly a Chrome extension is.
Chrome extensions really can be thought of as the way Google provides for extending the capabilities of Chrome.
Extensions are often confused with plugins which are quite different.
Many developers mistakenly confuse them as the same, but in a minute I'll show you the difference in Chrome itself.
There is quite a bit of debate across the web about the actual differences,
but the easy way to conceptualize it is to think of plugins as running outside of the sandbox context of
the browser and interacting with the browser. Extensions on the other hand, run within the browser
and conform to a specific set of APIs and capabilities exposed by Chrome.
This isn't to say that a Chrome extension can't ever do anything bad and it completely safe,
but you have a lot more assurance with most Chrome extensions that they're going to be safe to run,
especially if the extension is obtained from the Chrome Web Store.
Chrome extensions can be used for a variety of different purposes and can behave differently.
But, in general, Chrome extensions somehow expand the capabilities of the browser.
This could be through the creation of a sort of in-browser app that's accessed from the Chrome toolbar,
complete with its own UI, through injecting JavaScript into loaded pages,
or even changing some of the default behaviors of Chrome.