Now I want to show you a couple of different extensions just so you can get a basic idea of what
a Chrome extension is. So, you've probably already installed extensions in Chrome if you've used Chrome.
But, maybe you haven't. If you haven't ever installed any extensions in Chrome, you can usually find
extensions by going to the Chrome Web Store. So, if you go to chrome web store.
Inside here, this is a good place to find extensions if you just go to extension here.
And if you're not familiar with extensions already, I encourage you to take a look through here.
Especially if you use Chrome, there's quite a few really good extensions in here.
In fact, I need to go back through here and see if there's anything new that I might be able to utilize
that I've been missing. A lot of times extensions can really enhance the usage of Chrome because it can
give you some capabilities baked right into the browser that can really come in handy.
For example, I have a couple of extensions installed; one of them is the School of Voice extension
which I really like a lot because it lets me access my Google voice messages right here
and to even call and text someone.
And then I have this Bookmarking extension that automatically adds to my bookmark.
And so this is a pretty neat extension and this just shows you some of the capabilities of the extension
framework in Chrome. So for example, when I click this, it brings up my bookmarks and I can search it.
So, this has the extensions UI, but it also integrates
directly into this Omni bar in Chrome. So, if I hit * and then I type here.
So, I do let's say .NET. You can see that's actually searching my bookmarks and it's going to show me
what bookmarks are matching here. So, I can actually go to a bookmark directly from here.
You can see that is shows this Neat Bookmarks.
So, extensions really have a lot of different capabilities that we can utilize and we'll talk about
these more later. But, this should just you a basic idea of what extensions look like most of the time
you're interacting with them here in the browser. But, extensions don't actually have to be here in this
toolbar, some extensions are going to be running in the background and you won't actually even see them.
You can always see all the extensions that are running inside Chrome by going to this Manage here.
Or just doing chrome://extensions, you can just go to this in your browser and you'll see all your extensions.
And here you can actually see the Permissions for the extension, go to the website, you can allow them in
incognito mode and set the options on that. Or you can enable or you can delete the extensions.
So, you can see all the different extensions that I have here.
So, if you're not familiar with extensions at all, if you haven't ever used them in Chrome, I encourage you
to go to the Chrome Web Store and try a couple of extensions. Install them and get an idea of what extensions
can do and what extensions are out there before you continue with this course,
because that will help you when you're trying to learn about extensions.