I mentioned that I'd show you the difference between extension and a plugin just so you could see for yourself.
So, let's go ahead and take a quick look. So, it you do a chrome://extensions
you'll see all of the extensions here.
But, just to show you they are different, if you do chrome://plugins
you'll see that this is quite different. In fact, you have Adobe Flash Player as a common plugin
that ships with Chrome. And here if you hit this you can see the details, but your default view would be here
where you don't see the details. But, you can see that these are actual plugins and plugins are different
than extensions. These are going to be accessing your computer outside of the sandbox.
This could be a lot more dangerous. In fact, a lot of vulnerabilities come through the Flash plugin.
If you've heard of some of the exploits that have happened with some of the common browsers,
a lot of times it's through a plugin.
So, you can see that plugins are definitely not the preferred way to extend the capabilities of Chrome.
Now, sometimes you do need a plugin, sometimes you don't have a choice and you can, through an extension,
register a plugin, but we're not going to cover that in this course.
It is a rare occurrence though unless you're doing something like creating your own Flash Player or something
of the level of, for example, the Microsoft Office plugin which is able to launch Microsoft Office
documents from Chrome and things like that, you probably don't need to create a plugin.
You can probably create an extension instead which is a lot easier to do and is a lot safer.
So, if you want to ever see the difference, you can just go to extensions or plugins and here you can
manage either one of them.