As we talked about earlier, Chrome extensions use common web technologies like HTML, JavaScript, and CSS
to extend the capabilities of the Chrome browser. Chrome extensions work by extending the capabilities
of Chrome via some extension points which are defined in a manifest file that comes with extension
and through the use of JavaScript Chrome APIs. A Chrome behaves sort of like a JavaScript application
that Chrome runs and evokes at certain points which the developer of the extension can specify.
Chrome extensions can even run in the background and listen for events to trigger them.
Here is the basic process of how Chrome extensions are created and added to a browser.
Fist, a developer creates the extension using a combination of HTML, JavaScript, and CSS.
There are many ways these three technologies can be used to create an extension.
And a developer has access to many of the internal capabilities of Chrome through the Chrome APIs
which can be accessed from JavaScript. Then the HTML, JavaScript, and CSS files are packaged together
with a manifest file that specifies important information about how the extension should work and what files
it contains. This is all packaged into a zipped file with the .CRX extension.
Typically, at this point, the CRX file is deployed to either the Chrome Web Store or some other location
that users can access and download the extension from. We'll cover how to do this in the last module.
Then finally, the extension is installed into the user's browser.
Chrome automatically recognizes the .CRX extension and knows how to unpack it and read the manifest file
to determine how exactly to integrate the extension into the browser.
At this point, the extension is completely installed on the user's machine and integrated with the browser.
This is important because it's a common misconception that Chrome extensions run from the web.
Because they seem to magically appear when you install Chrome on another computer and sign in with your
Google account. And that's it! At a very basic level Chrome extensions really are that simple.