Okay, so now you know what a Chrome extension is and a bit about how Chrome extensions work.
But, what exactly can you do with a Chrome extension? Chrome extensions are actually very powerful and can
do more than you might think. Let's go over some of the obvious and the not so obvious things you can do
with a Chrome extension. First of all, you can interact with web pages in the browser or external web pages
and/or other servers. This means that you can have an extension interact with APIs or other services to
perform its functionality. You aren't restricted to just what you can package in your extension file.
You can also control many of the browser features available in Chrome.
We'll take a look at the Chrome APIs in a minute, but there're pretty extensive and really lets you do a lot
more than you might have thought possible. For example, through the Chrome APIs you can access things the
Font settings, Tabs, Downloads, and even History. You can also add your own UI to Chrome through the use of
either a Chrome Browser action or Page action. Browser actions show a button on the Chrome toolbar that can
be pressed to display a custom UI. And page actions can put icons in the address bar that can be clicked to
access a user interface for actions specific to that page. In addition, your extension can have its own
options page where it can be configured through your own custom UI.
Extensions can modify loaded pages by injecting JavaScript into the page to add capabilities to the page or
even change the UI of it. You can also use extensions to add context menu items to the right-click
context menu in Chrome. Finally, Chrome extensions can actually load DLLs.
Although this is something you typically want to avoid since it's pretty dangerous and causes an extension to
leave the safe sandbox environment of Chrome. Doing this actually creates a real plugin using the NPAPI,
but we won't be covering that in this course.