Now I did want to show you where you can get access to information about the Chrome APIs that we're going to
be using in the course and I want to give you a quick overview of what's available just so you can see
how powerful the Chrome APIs are and how much you can actually do with your extensions.
So, if you go to developers.google.com it will take you to this page and here you can click on Chrome extensions.
From here you can read about extensions, we're going to cover a lot of this material in this course,
but one thing that you might want to check out is this Reference portion here.
This has some really useful information. Specifically let's look at this chrome.*APIs.
So, this is all of the APIs that are available through Chrome. And here you can see that there are quite a
few different things in here that you can access.
For example, we could go to events and then you can see that we have this chrome.events.
And this gives some documentation on the chrome.events API to basically let you subscribe to events.
So, you can utilize this in yours extensions. And it has some good documentation on all of this.
So, you can go through this chrome.*APIs to find out exactly what you can do with Chrome.
Chances are if there is something in Chrome that you want to do with your extension, you can probably
find out how to do it through here.
You can access really most of Chrome through this.
And throughout this course we'll just be using a sub-set of the Chrome APIs.
There's so much of the Chrome APIs, obviously we can't cover all of them in this course.
But, once you know how to use some of the basic APIs, it'll be easy to go to this page and look at any other
APIs that you want to use and figure out how to use those.