There are three main options for deploying your extension, we'll cover each of these in detail, but let's
go over them from a high level first. The first option is self-hosted.
With this option, you are creating your own extension package and putting it somewhere for users to access
and install in Chrome. There are certain security requirements you have to be aware of for this option,
but we'll talk about those in a little bit. Next up is normal Chrome Web Store deployment.
In this case, you put your extension in the Chrome Web Store where users can either browse to find it or
use a specific link to download and install it. Updates are also automatically handled in this case,
just like Chrome updates happen automatically for the browser itself.
Finally, we have a combination, where you put your extension in the Chrome Web Store, but you actually let
users install the extension from your own site. In this scenario, you maintain control over the distribution
of your extension, but you get the benefits in security of the Chrome Web Store hosting it for you.