Now let's see how we can create an actual extension package; right now we've been using our extensions just
by pointing Chrome at a directory and it's been reading it from there, but you may want to actually pack
your extension, either to do self-hosting or just to test it out, maybe you want to be able to give it to
someone to be able to test it. So what we can do here is from Extensions, we can just click this
‘Pack Extension' and this is pretty easy.
All we're going to do is just browse to where our Extension directory is, so in my case it's under here,
and we're going to take, let's say, our Pluralsight Helper and we'll just click OK,
and then when I click ‘Pack Extension', it's going to go ahead and it's created this .crx file and it's also
created this PluralsightHelper.pem - this is my key file. This is important to keep because it is a private key
that was used to sign this extension. So if I want to update this, I need to have this file.
So let's go ahead and take a look here.
Now on the file system you can see we have this crx and we have this .pem, and the crx file format is
actually a zip file format that has a header that has some additional information in it as well.
And now let's say that I made some changes to my extension; let's say that I update the version number
in my manifest file, so let's go ahead and edit this real quick.
And let's say we have a new version, we have version 1.1. So now I could just save this
and then I'm going to want to update this,
so what I would do is just do ‘Pack my extension' and then I would actually browse
to this private key file,
and now when I click ‘Pack Extension', it of course gives me a warning that there's already a cx file
present with this name and I'm going to proceed anyway,
and so now I have my updated extension. So that's how to pack it; it's really, really easy to do.