Self-hosting is not quite as easy as it used to be, as the newer versions of Chrome have made it more
difficult to install an extension that isn't from the Chrome Web Store.
As a result, you should only really use self-hosting if you have to, because it's more difficult and
error-prone than the other options, plus it's less secure for users.
Extensions, of course, can do many bad things, so it makes sense that Google would encourage using the
Chrome Web Store for distribution, but if you do want to do self-hosting or you have to, here are some
things to be aware of. First, you'll want to configure autoupdate in your manifest file.
You can find instructions on how to do this here. It involves creating an entry in your manifest file,
as well as creating another xml manifest that you use to indicate what the current version is and where
to download the extension. This will ensure that your extension gets updated automatically.
When using web store, you don't have to worry about this. Next, you need to allow your extension to be
installed from your site. By default, Chrome blocks all extensions from being installed that don't have
explicit permissions specified for the domain that extension is coming from.
You could follow this link to see how to set those permissions for each operating system.
This requirement is probably the biggest reason self-hosting is a hassle; it requires actually modifying
the Chrome install itself. Next, you need to make sure you keep your private key that was used when you
packaged the extension. This is required to update the extension.
And finally, you can actually install an extension without the extra security change to the extension
install source if it's manually done. This can be done by opening up the Settings page in Chrome and
manually dragging the crx file into it. If you have to have your extension self-hosted and you can't
modify the extension install source for the user's Chrome installation, you may need to resort to this approach.