So I just want to show you real quick what happens if you try to install an extension.
So I'm going to go to our PluralsightHelper.crx and I'm just going to drag this right into Chrome here,
and I'm going to go ahead and say Continue. This might harm my computer, sure, that's fine, and then you
can see that it says "Apps, extensions, and user scripts cannot be added from this website."
So, basically unless I have that permission set that we talked about, we can't even install this just by
clicking this from a website. You can imagine if you downloaded this from a particular site, you wouldn't
be able to run and install this, but what you can do is if you do have the Settings open in this Extension tab,
then you can drag it into here and then you see this drop to install, and then it'll ask about the permissions
and let you add it. So a user can manually add this and this is useful to know for testing if you're trying
to test out your package; you can do it, you just have to go through here, but it's definitely not a route
that most users are going to know about, so you don't want to really host a crx file on your site and then
expect a user to read some instructions that are going to tell them to download the file, save it somewhere else,
open up the Settings, and then drag and drop it. So, that's really the way that I think Google is pushing us
to use the Chrome Web Store, but it's really not that bad as we'll see in a little bit when I show you how
to use the Chrome Web Store; it's pretty nice and pretty easy to get an extension in there.