Alright, so let's take a look at the Chrome Developer Dashboard and how we would actually upload an app.
So the easiest way to get there is probably just to type in chrome developer dashboard into Google,
because you can see the URL here is chrome.google.com/webstore/developer/dashboard,
so that's a little bit hard to type in.
And when you go there, you'll need to authenticate with a Google account, so you can see that I'm signed
in to my main Gmail account. And let's go ahead and go back to the Dashboard, and here at this Dashboard,
you can see any of the extensions I've already published or apps, chrome web store apps, I just have the
Pluralsight Helper, which I've already tried to publish, so I've already just put this out here and it can be
accessed from a link and we have some information about the developer account and some basic settings you can modify.
Now all you have to do is click this ‘Add new Item',
and then it'll have you upload an extension or app and it says a .zip file, so one thing to make note of
here is this first item - it says "Upload a ZIP file of your item directory, not a packaged CRX file."
So you don't want to upload the CRX file, and part of the reason for that is because the web store's
actually going to package it for you, and remember, we have this whole signing with the private key,
well it's going to be signing it based on some security credentials on your Google account so that you won't
have to actually include your own private key. Just by uploading your app or your extension through your account,
Google will know that it's you. So, what we're going to do is we're just going to go to
our directory and all we basically have to do in here is to zip this up.
So I'm just going to go to Creating Chrome Extension, let's go ahead and do, let's say our Protein Tracker.
So I'm just going to do a zip here, just ProteinTracker.zip, so now I have this zip file and all I'm going
to do is choose this file. So I'm just going to go in here and we will find our
ProteinTracker.zip, then we just click Upload,
and then it will take us to our Edit Items screen where we can edit everything here, and it has pretty good descriptions.
You can see that I don't have an icon so it's not showing my icon here.
We can put in our detailed description, we can upload a new icon here, and it has all the details about
the particular icon sizes. There's a lot here to pay attention to if you want to get everything just right,
but it's really important if you're making an extension that's going to be downloaded by other people and
you want to have it look nice, you'll probably want to follow all these instructions.
Same thing with the screenshots; you can link to a YouTube video, which is probably a good idea to show
how to use your extension. It also has these Promotional tile images; these are those images that you see
in the Chrome Web Store; again, good if you're trying to market this.
And then the tile previews. And then here is an important part — this is where you verify that this is
an item for your website. So, it's going to show me any of the verified sites that I have connected with
this account, so my simpleprogrammer.com, for example, I could use that here.
I can also put a link to my website or to my Support in FAQ for this chrome extension if I have one here.
Then you want to select a category and this can be whatever category that you have.
Let's put this under Fun and then you can decide what regions you want your extension to be available in.
The language; you do have to select a language. A lot of these other options are optional, you don't have
to specify a lot of these things, but you do need a language. And then you can actually hook up your Google Analytics here.
Now what this will do is this is going to basically just track the usage of this extension, but not the usage
inside the extension. What I mean is you're going to be able to track how many people are downloading and
using the extension, not actually what they're doing in the extension.
And then we have any requirements that are specified in the manifest file and then this little thing for
ads behavior. If you're injecting ads, that's probably not a good idea, but --- and then the visibility options here.
Now this is going to control how you're going to be able to distribute this.
So, the default is all Chrome Web Store users; that's going to make it so your extension is visible just
in the Chrome Web Store. You can just say people with the link, which will hide it so that someone has to
has to have the link. It's not a secure way of having your app be in the web store — you can't count on
no one being able to get access to it that you don't allow, but this is a way to; for example, if you have
a company extension but you want to distribute it through the Chrome Web Store, this is a great way to do it
because it's not going to show up when people search for it. And then trusted testers; you can set up
tester accounts that you can manage from that Developer Dashboard and you can just set this up just for
people to be able to test it. So then all you have to do is you can either Save draft and return to
Dashboard or you can just preview it or publish it right here.
So we could actually save our draft and we could click Publish if we want to publish this;
I'm not going to publish this at this point, because we don't really want to actually publish this, but that's
pretty much it. It's really simple, really easy to get this setup and to get an extension in the Chrome Web Store.