Now this is one of my favorite ways to deploy your extension. This approach is a combination approach we
talked about earlier; the official name is the inline installation.
In this case, we'll host our extension with the Chrome Web Store, but we'll add some code to our page to
allow a user to install it directly from our site. To do this, it's not very hard at all.
First, you need to, of course, have your extension deployed in the Chrome Web Store, then you just add the
link in your head tag of your page that links to the Chrome Web Store with your extensions unique ID.
Finally, you can just call chrome.webstore.install to allow the user to install the extension in some JavaScript code.
There are a couple of other restrictions that you should know about though.
First, you need to make sure your site is verified with the Google Site Master Tools, and second,
the user has to initiate the action for your call to chrome.webstore.install.
So in other words, you can't just run this script when someone comes to your page; they have to click
a button or do something else to initiate it. You can find the complete documentation with all the details
at this link, but it's pretty simple and easy to do.