Alright, so let's go ahead and see how we can actually debug some of our extensions.
So, if you already are familiar with the Chrome Developer Tools, you may have used them on a web page,
so for example, I could right-click on something here and say ‘Inspect element' and this would bring them up
and I can also just bring up the Chrome Developer Tools from either the menu if I go under Tools and then
go to Developer tools or the JavaScript console, but you may have used these tools to debug web pages,
to change the html or the CSS or just to go through the JavaScript and figure out what's going on and
you may have found that you're not actually seeing the extension JavaScript or the extension HTML inside here.
So, you can actually use the Chrome Developer Tools, but you just need a different instance.
So, for example, let's take a look at our Protein Tracker extension.
If I were to right-click in here, I can do an ‘Inspect element' and this will work.
I can also just right-click on the extension itself in the toolbar and say ‘Inspect popup' and that will go
ahead and bring up the popup, as well as another Chrome Developer Tool console.
So this one is actually operating against this particular page; so if we were to go to Elements here,
you can see that it is working for our popup, our user interface here, and then from here we could look at
our sources and we can find all of the actual source here; this popup.js, for example, and we can do
anything we want with this JavaScript. So, just being able to see what's loaded up is step one,
that's one really useful thing to be able to do to debug an extension.
In many cases you can figure out what's going wrong with your extension by looking here and seeing if
there's something missing, is this JavaScript correct, can you see what's happening with this HTML?
For example, you could go in here and you could change the HTML or the CSS styling if you wanted to.
So let's go ahead and change the style for this; for example, let's say that the element.style for this
should be font-size and we'll make this small, so you can see that this actually changes to small.
So that's how we get at our actual extension when we have this visible page UI.