Now let's look at an example of how you might actually utilize this to figure out something that might be
going on here; so for example, what we can do here with our Protein Tracker is we can go to our Sources
and this popup.js, and from here, we can actually make some changes or set breakpoints.
So, let's go ahead and just set a breakpoint here and let's say that we want to figure out what's going on.
Let's set a breakpoint, let's say right there. So now what we can do is we can basically type in something here
and click this ‘Add Protein' and you'll see that we're hitting this breakpoint, so we're actually debugging
this in this JavaScript debugger, and we can do all kinds of things like we can look at our scope variables.
So here we have our local variable, so we can see what the amount - it's set to 123, we can see our items,
we can basically go through here and even step through this if we wanted to.
And we're not going to go through all of the features of the Chrome Developer Tools here, but you basically
have the entire capability of the Chrome Developer Tools at your disposal to be able to debug these extensions.
So if you know how to use the Chrome Developer Tools, and I'll show you in a minute a resource that you can
use to find out more about it, but if you do use the Chrome Developer Tools, you'll find that debugging
an extension really isn't much different than debugging any web page.