So I wanted to show you one more thing real quick that I find really useful for debugging an extension and
this will apply to some of the other pages that we'll look at in our extension debugging in a little bit here,
but it's one of the things that a lot of developers forget that they can do when debugging an extension.
And I find this really useful. So let's go ahead and go through here and we'll just let this continue and
get rid of this breakpoint.
But now I'm going to click on this console and we can actually bring it up in here as well just by clicking
this so that we can have a split view.
But what we can do with this console is we can basically enter any JavaScript in here, so we could do things
like perform selectors, jQuery selectors, we can actually manipulate the DOM, we can basically run JavaScript,
we have a console in here, and one really useful thing that you can do is you can use the chrome object.
Remember that the chrome API is basically chrome.whatever and so you can actually practice or try utilizing
or experiment with chrome API calls from here. So, for example, remember we have like this browserAction,
so we could actually do browserAction, and we could actually do something like get the popup or get the title
or even set the popup or title, setBadgeText, so we could try doing that; we can basically do anything we
could do with that API, which is really neat because you can sort of experiment with some of the API calls
in order to build out your extensions. So maybe you have part of the functionality of your extension and
you want to try to do something in it and you don't want to have to make changes to your actual extension
and then reload it to test it out, you can test out that logic sort of right inside here and see what's going on.
Another useful thing that I tend to do is to go into my source code and then let's say that I'm having
a problem that isn't working; for example, trying to do this sync.get.
Well I could just copy this code that's not working, I can put it into the console, so let's go ahead and do
that real quick, and then, for example, in this callback here, I could change this, do like a console debug
in here to write it out or figure out what's going on a lot easier.
So, I utilize this quite often to be able to troubleshoot pieces of my code.