Okay, so that's the basics of doing debugging for our UI pages, but you may need to get at some background pages.
So, for example, we have an eventPage for our Protein Tracker and then for our Pluralsight extension,
we have some pages as well. So let's take a look and see how we can get to those.
So, for example, let's look at our Pluralsight extension.
If I go to this Top 100 Leaderboard here, if I right-click on our extension,
I can do an ‘Inspect popup' and then I'm going to be able to access this extension here, so this one makes sense,
and this is pretty easy — you probably won't have much trouble figuring that out, but let's suppose you want
to get to those event pages behind this. Well the way to do that is you can just go
to your Settings and then go to Extensions, and then from here, if you look at each one of these extensions,
let's take our Pluralsight Helper, for example; it has this "Inspect views: generated background page.html."
So what we can do here is we can click on this,
and then this should bring up our developer tools for that eventPage, and what you'll notice is that actually
what happens is Chrome generates a background_page.html that just has a body that has your script in here
that has your source for your eventPage. You can, of course, create an HTML page with an eventPage if you want to,
but Chrome will just generate this for you. But what we can do now is we can go in here and we can look at
this eventPage.js and this is our actual JavaScript, and again, we can set breakpoints in here if we want to;
so, for example, let's say we set a breakpoint on that, then we go over here, and then we reload this page.
You can see that we're hitting this breakpoint — we got this request, action, which is set to show,
so it's about to show our actual extension. So you could do this with anything that you have as a background_page,
and of course, you could have multiple background pages, so you could use this for whatever background pages
you have and you can open up multiple Chrome Developer Tool windows in order to be able to debug back and forth
when you're sending messages back and forth. And I do want to remind you also though, don't forget that
sometimes it's easiest to just go ahead and do something as simple as do alert(‘hi').
I mean this isn't the best practice for debugging some complex JavaScript, but occasionally it makes sense
to just do something really easy, really visible; just put in your code and run this, and this is going to
prove that you got to this point, that you don't have to open up the console.
You can also do things like debug right in here that will set a debugger, set a breakpoint automatically
or logging to the Chrome console, which you can do just by doing console.log, and then specifying your message.