Okay, and there's one other type of script, which we haven't talked about so far, which is a content script.
Now these content scripts get injected into the page, so you can actually debug them directly from the
Developer console for the page. So, for example, with our Top 100 Leaderboard, if I go in here and I go to
Sources in the Developer tools, you'll notice that there is this Content tab.
Inside here, these are the unique IDs for each extension. So if we look through these, we can probably find our extension.
And you can see that our extension is actually this first one and you can see the scripts are loaded,
including our Pluralsight_cs.js. So we can actually debug in here as well, so you just have to remember that
the content scripts are going to be part of the page, so you're going to debug them like part of the page.
For the UI stuff, you're going to either just right-click on this and do ‘Inspect element' or you can
right-click and do ‘Inspect popup',
and then for the background pages, you do have to reach that from the Extensions screen.